They don't see what I see.
Tinker Bell and the Legend of the NeverBeast is a adventure,
animation, family film directed by Steve Loter.
An ancient myth of a massive creature sparks the curiosity of Tinker Bell and her good friend
Fawn, an animal fairy who’s not afraid to break the rules to help an animal in need.
But this creature is not welcome in Pixie Hollow — and the scout fairies are determined
to capture the mysterious beast, who they fear will destroy their home.
Fawn must convince her fairy friends to risk
everything to rescue the NeverBeast.
Fawn (voice), played by Ginnifer Goodwin.
Tinker Bell (voice), played by Mae Whitman.
Nyx (voice), played by Rosario Dawson.
Silvermist (voice), played by Lucy Liu.
Iridessa (voice), played by Raven-Symoné.
Rosetta (voice), played by Megan Hilty.
Tinker Bell and the Legend of the NeverBeast is a 2015 American
animated fantasy film directed by Steve Loter.
It is the sixth installment in the Tinker Bell film series,
based on the character Tinker Bell from J.
Barrie's Peter Pan.
This was the final feature film to be produced by Disneytoon
Studios three years before its closure on June 28, 2018.
It is also the last of the direct to video Disney
follow-ups after a 21-year-long run.
Mae Whitman, Lucy Liu, Raven-Symoné, Megan Hilty, Pamela Adlon, and Anjelica Huston reprise
their roles of Tinker Bell, Silvermist, Iridessa, Rosetta, Vidia and Queen Clarion.
Ginnifer Goodwin joins the cast, replacing Angela Bartys as the voice of Fawn in
this film, Rosario Dawson joins the cast as new character Nyx.
Singer Mel B also joins the cast as new character Fury in the British
release while Danai Gurira voices her in the American release.
The film explores themes of fairy tale, fairy, tinkerbell.